Theft of any vehicle, be it scooter or car, has become a
common thing these days. If a
vehicle is stolen at any place, then fear creeps into the
minds of all the people living in that area
just by hearing the name of the story
and many people are unaware that
brother, if our cycle is stolen, be it a
car or scooter and it may be any other work, then
how do we delete the servicing from it
and today in this video,
according to some sources, when you watch the video, if
any of your vehicles is stolen or
any officer's vehicle is stolen in your area, then in
that case, the other part of that theft, that is, the
corner of the beard, will be
read by the textured step, due to which
nothing wrong will happen to it and there will be no
problem till the insurance company or if
your vehicle is found, if
your vehicle is found in the police station, then
how can you take the vehicle from the scanner police,
I will definitely tell you the entire process of that thing in this video,
you
must watch the entry of the video, my name is this, you are
watching Smart Aligarh, so first of all let's
talk about yesterday
What things can we do in case of theft and how
should we be aware, I will tell you a very urgent thing in the video center, I will make
you aware because if you get to know
all this information from the chief guy inside the bar market, then
all the people will
only loot you, that is, they will make such demands and
pressurize you with such things that they will
try to extract money from your husband, so
you are absolutely
safe from all these frauds, Kaya, and you will stay safe, first of all the
police must watch the video till the end,
then I will
tell you all the details in the end, first of all what will be your main work,
for example, if you
live in your house and you
park any of your vehicles outside your house, be it my
car or any vehicle or any
two wheeler or four wheeler, whatever is inside it, gets
stolen from your house, then what will be the
first thing you will do in its name, so the
first thing that has to be done in your jurisdiction will be the
police station, police
station and superintendent of police means the
place where you live and
whichever police station is near your house, you have to file an FIR there.
The first thing you have to do is to
tell this to the FIR side, you have to pay attention to this thing,
like you get the FIR done, secondly, the date,
place and time, like if
your car was stolen at night, then you should
tell inside the police station that I
came to my house at this time and at this time I
parked my car here and
went inside my house and I can be found here, that is,
tell the date and time, at what time did I
park the car, the place
I live at and at this time I came home,
you have to write these three things in your FIR,
after this you have to write the vehicle number and
chassis number and engine number, all these things you would have
written in your RC, which is your Mangal ki Aarti, for that
you will have to write the vehicle number, chassis number and engine number in your FIR, but
if the police tell you your name, then you
must keep these things in mind, so these small
things will be useful for you in taking the claim from the insurance company in future, that is why
I have
told you that you will have to write the vehicle number, chassis and engine
number, my brother, yesterday's
theft, now for the second major
time  A very important thing comes up that it is
difficult and
problematic for example if you have a
car added in your name and you have your name
written in it but if you have a car in your father's name
or a car in the name of any relative of yours
and if you are going to file an FIR
in the police station then
you have to pay attention to getting the
name of the person in whose name the car is registered written in the
copy of the FIR because for
example when the FIR is written you will feel a little
nervous and if by
mistake while going to file this FIR you have got your name written
wrongly then there can be some problem so
after this let me tell you that whoever turns out to be the person
you have to write his name in the copy of your FIR, the
second thing comes up in the hard work,
when you go to this police
station centre i.e. the nearest police station then
you have to get a
certified copy of the FIR from your police station officer, you will get a certified
copy of the FIR from your father who would be doing the registration.
Now in this
I have talked about the second important thing,
if someone from outside your house is
weak then he should talk about him.  Tell me, but you
yourself have gone for a trip, brother, yesterday, wherever
you went for a trip, keep your car parked
somewhere there and if
your car gets stolen, then in that case,
where will you take your officer to the
police station, where you had parked your car, the place where you had gone for a trip, you will have to file an FIR at the nearest police station of that area, you will
not have to file an FIR near your house at all because it can be
found here,
you have to file an FIR in the police station near the place where the car was stolen, you have done it friends,
now after this you have to directly do 124,
you have to inform the insurance company
that I have insured my car with your company
and my car has been
stolen, you have to inform your insurance company through various methods, even if
you confirm by calling, like
calling their customer care, emailing,
posting a letter, whatever you do, you
must inform them through 1984 and get a
complaint number with you
because whichever insurance company you want to inform about
this theft  They tell you the details, if you
tell them your complaint then they will give you a complaint number,
so you should take your complaint number from
Vid Flirts, though the company says that
we have to inform you within 24 hours, so
you have to call 1234, you have to inform,
call, email, post this letter
to both, now you receive this complaint number,
now we will talk about it for two minutes, you have informed the
life insurance company about the graphics of the police station,
now
two things will come out of it, first thing if you have a
police officer, that is, the police station in which
you have written the complaint, do a very
good job in the cases, investigate, if the
police find something in your car, then they will
not give you any trouble at all, they will not stop you at all,
you will have to first go to the advocate,
you have to
investigate the matter, the police will investigate it and if
you find it, then you have to contact the advocate, you have to
go to the advocate, you have to tell all your
details that I have done this method at
this place, at this time I have done my  The car was parked, the
next day you pick it up, my car is missing, the
car has been stolen, then you will
tell all this to the advocate, by
Robert Hook,
tell me that I have got the affidavit done, see this is
my number and in which
police station, what is the name of the police station and this is the
name of my police station, that is, FIR number,
name of the police station, you tell the advocate, then the
advocates of yours will type a complaint
in the court, that is, they will file a complaint, an
application in Faridabad and with the
help of section 1431 and 57 CrPC, the
advocates will file the application in the
court, that is, an application has to be filed
that our brother's car was stolen and
in the police station where we had filed the complaint, the
police operation had found our wire
and then the court will order that the
police officer should deliver it to us, that is, the owner, to whom the
complaint was filed, so
this is the process,
you will have to follow this because if
any officer in any police station
finds your car, then immediately you will get the car
You will not get it back, you have to follow this process,
so after following this process the
doctor will inform the police officer that
you should give the car to them,
well you will get your car, whatever will not be there, it will be
completed by the person who had got it done, now
ask for it inside it, come on friend brother, you got the car, the
police officer means how much time has passed, the
police officer, the investigation
officer caught the thief and your car was
also not found, you use it inside it, now
we will take the insurance company's dream and bloody,
now the insurance that we have done for our
car, so this my
car has been stolen, then from that we should
ask for a claim from our insurance company, so
how do you know its meaning, a small
format and you will have to understand there,
asked for the insurance claim answer, then you will have to
take a certified copy of the FIR, a certified copy of your affair, which I
told you like this that you will have to take a copy of the affair,
then the decided copy is the duty of every police
officer, there is class two of section 144, the
pure sequence of things is written, the
third off and the certified copy of the affair in every police station is
given  which does not know how to write, then in this there is a
certified copy of the FIR, your
applicant ad, common man and a copy of your insurance, all
these documents, a
copy of the sapphire, Banarasi and a
copy of your insurance, you have to submit
all the documents to your insurance company
that our car was stolen
and this was our complaint number and we had
also told it to our police station and
our car has not been found in the police station till now, due to
this our
claim is pending, so all these documents of ours have been
submitted to you or
whenever you submit all your documents in MS Word scanning,
after that
you will get the ID of the insurance company, the ID
being the should declared value amount, when you get the
insurance done in your insurance company, then you have to enter the ID in every insurance,
you will get the amount of the should declared value,
now apart from this, there is one thing that the insurance
company people are very cunning, they will
tell you any reason and
cancel your insurance, no brother,
whatever you  The person was supposed to get the money but it did
not come. If there is a problem with your insurance
or if there is a lack of documents, then whatever
documents I tell you from your side, apart from this document, the
code is not applicable. If this
half inch person stops your case by telling you some fault,
then what will you do? Simple, you
can file a case with the help of an advocate in the consumer forum because the new
percent will give you hundred percent.
When you take the case to the consumer forum, the case
progresses very quickly, the case
process is not long. Simple, the
consumer forum will make you smile and tell you that
brother, my car was stolen. I had
submitted all my documents to the Swiss company, even then
yesterday my
finance company has stopped my work by giving invalid fault.
So when you go to these authorities, the
hundred percent consumer forum will definitely give you the hundred percent consumer forum and there are many
cases under this, this is the only chance left for the
consumer that he should
go to the consumer forum.  And you will get your flame back.
Select hundred percent of the claim.
Now, in this video, I am going to
end with one thing that I
told you that the
entire process of the house is that you have
found your car inside Jaipur station and
then you will take it from here. If it is
not found inside the police station, then
how will you claim from the insurance company? If
we have given a long notice in this lineage, then you
can go to the consumer forum in Jaipur and take your claim. The entire process is that if
your car gets stolen, then
after your car is stolen, you go through the first step
or at least some people, so I hope that
you have understood it in this video today.
If such an incident happens with any of your close relatives or you,
your vehicle gets
stolen, then you should take this step and take each
step carefully, keeping one thing in mind,
leave yourself an inch and take care of your
issues and take your rights,
get them. The
main thing is that all these things,
I have talked about one main issue that whenever
you use this imagination  If you
ride a bicycle, then you will have to keep all these
papers complete in it, your house will have to be
kept proper,
you will have to do pollution, you will have to take precautions
because the amount that you were supposed to get from the chairperson gets
wasted, why do you lose it?
Suppose if your house gets stolen and you have
not done the insurance, then the money that you were supposed to get for the ID
value, for which
if you are away, then that person becomes someone else,
just in the
pursuit of saving a little money, so I would request all of you to
follow the complete proper rules of your brother, keep yourself
established and do your pollution,
because of this, by chance, if you have any money of yours, then
you are absolutely entitled to
use your rights and you
can openly consider any of your money
for whatever you are entitled to, so I hope
that you liked this video,
if you get any, then you
must tell me in the comment section, you can
message me on Instagram and send personal
questions, absolutely
all your questions will be answered.  I will answer all of them. If
you like the video, then you
must like and share the video and if
you want such videos based
on practical questions,
then you must tell me and you
must subscribe to the channel. Thank you, thank you
[Sangeet]